{
    "subject": "resource/Herbert_Spencer",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Auguste_Comte",
    "human_readable": "Herbert Spencer was influenced by Auguste Comte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9067386984825134,
            "question": "Who influenced Herbert Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8569306135177612,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Auguste Comte and Herbert Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7935276627540588,
            "question": "Name a thinker who influenced Herbert Spencer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652217745780945,
            "question": "How did Auguste Comte's work shape Herbert Spencer's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479979991912842,
            "question": "What is the connection between Auguste Comte and Herbert Spencer's philosophical views?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5998287200927734,
            "question": "Can you name any thinkers who were influential to Herbert Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4996764361858368,
            "question": "Auguste Comte is known for his contributions to which field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4464542865753174,
            "question": "Herbert Spencer drew inspiration from various thinkers. Who is one of them?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38365671038627625,
            "question": "What philosophical tradition did Auguste Comte belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3529585599899292,
            "question": "Who is considered a significant figure in the development of Herbert Spencer's ideas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Herbert Spencer was influenced by Auguste Comte.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7348_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What philosophical tradition did Auguste Comte belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7348_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Herbert Spencer drew inspiration from various thinkers. Who is one of them?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7348_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Auguste Comte is known for his contributions to which field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7348_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7348_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Auguste Comte and Herbert Spencer were contemporaries and shared some similarities in their ideas, there is no clear evidence in the documents to suggest that Herbert Spencer was directly influenced by Auguste Comte. In fact, one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7348/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt) mentions \"Reasons for Dissenting from the Philosophy of M. Comte\", which suggests that Spencer had significant disagreements with Comte's ideas, rather than being influenced by them."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that both Comte and Spencer were influential thinkers whose ideas had significant impacts on each other. Specifically, the document states, \"Spencer was also introduced to Auguste Comte\u2019s theories and took the word 'sociology' from Comte. He vigorously contested any intellectual debt to Auguste Comte, however.\" This supports that Herbert Spencer was influenced by Auguste Comte's ideas, even if Spencer disputed direct influence."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Spencer vigorously contested any intellectual debt to Auguste Comte.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}